Survival was just the beginning.
The Strangers: Chapter 2 is a horror, thriller film directed by Renny Harlin.
When The Strangers learn that one of their victims, Maya, is still
alive, they return to finish what they’ve started.
Maya, played by Madelaine Petsch.
Ryan, played by Froy Gutierrez.
Gregory, played by Gabriel Basso.
Shelly, played by Ema Horvath.
Nurse Danica, played by Brooke Lena Johnson.
Sheriff Rotter, played by Richard Brake.
The Strangers – Chapter 2 is a 2025 American horror film serving as the fourth film in The Strangers film
series, and the second installment of a new trilogy following The Strangers: Chapter 1 (2024).
The film was directed by Renny Harlin, and stars Madelaine Petsch, Gabriel
Basso, Froy Gutierrez, Ema Horvath, and Ella Bruccoleri.
The film had its Hollywood premiere September 16, 2025, and was released in
the United States by Lionsgate Films on September 26, 2025.
The film explores themes of ambulance, sequel, hospital, slasher, reboot.
The tone is dark and intense.